<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">DroneSim</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="launch_drone">Launch Drone</string>
    <string name="disable_drone">Disable Drone</string>
    <string name="drone_speed">Drone speed:</string>
    <string name="drone_lat">Drone latitude:</string>
    <string name="drone_long">Drone longitude:</string>
    <string name="title_activity_test_map">TestMapActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_game_screen">GameScreenActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_drone_control">DroneControlActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_use_case_selection">UseCaseSelectionActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_results_screen">ResultsScreenActivity</string>
    <string name="government_use_case_description">The forest fire example is a case of using the drone as a first responder in order to have awareness of the situation. Government uses of drones are primarily concerned with public safety, with them being used for search and rescue, disaster assessment/recovery and border security.</string>
    <string name="agriculture_use_case_description">Drones have many uses in the agriculture industry including livestock, herd or wildlife management as seen in this example. Other agriculture use cases include monitoring crops and fields, managing coastal fisheries and monitoring the organic status of crop or livestock producers.</string>
    <string name="insurance_use_case_description">What you saw with the building with fire damage is an example of damage assessment for insurance industry. Other drone uses for the insurance industry include technical enablers that facilitate the capture, storage and analysis of UAV data and use by large insurance companies.</string>
    <string name="media_use_case_description">The example illustrates the sports game coverage for the media industry, although this is just one of many media drone use cases. Other media use cases in clude live streaming news broadcasts, breaking news coverage, and data analytics.</string>
    <string name="energy_use_case_description">The energy use case seen in this demo is plant monitoring of a solar panel installation, but there are other energy-related use cases as well. These include data analytics for public utilities, oil or gas pipeline monitoring, pole and line monitoring and exploration research for new wells and resources.</string>
    <string name="healthcare_use_case_description">The primary use case of drones for the healthcare industry is the rapid transportation of emergency supplies and communications/video capabilities connecting hospitals to the scene of the incident, as seen with this example. There is also some overlap with the government use cases, such as first responder for situational awareness.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_completion">CompletionActivity</string>
    <string name="config_dweet_name">DroneConfig</string>
    <string name="controller_dweet_name">DweetController</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tutorial">TutorialActivity</string>
    <string name="tutorial_government_use_case">Government</string>
    <string name="tutorial_government_game_use_case">Wildfire assessment</string>
    <string name="tutorial_government_use_case_description">Analyze the current state of a wildfire in order for firefighters to safely contain the fire</string>
    <string name="tutorial_government_game_description">Move the drone to the goal marker without steering the drone into the fire</string>
    <string name="tutorial_government_image1_text">Your drone marker, control with arrow keys</string>
    <string name="tutorial_government_image2_text">The goal marker, steer the drone to this to complete the game</string>
    <string name="tutorial_government_image3_text">Avoid steering the drone into the fire</string>
    <string name="tutorial_agriculture_use_case">Agriculture</string>
    <string name="tutorial_agriculture_game_use_case">Livestock inspection</string>
    <string name="tutorial_agriculture_use_case_description">Gather the data from each of the livestock animals to see if they are healthy</string>
    <string name="tutorial_agriculture_game_description">Move the drone marker to all of the moving animal markers</string>
    <string name="tutorial_agriculture_image1_text">Your drone marker, control with the arrow keys</string>
    <string name="tutorial_agriculture_image2_text">An animal marker, move the drone to its circle to gather data</string>
    <string name="tutorial_insurance_use_case">Insurance</string>
    <string name="tutorial_insurance_game_use_case">Building damage assessment</string>
    <string name="tutorial_insurance_use_case_description">An earthquake just hit Los Angeles, and you need to analyze the damage of a building</string>
    <string name="tutorial_insurance_game_description">Move the drone to a room in the building to analyze it, visit all rooms to complete the game</string>
    <string name="tutorial_insurance_image1_text">Your drone marker, control with arrow keys</string>
    <string name="tutorial_insurance_image2_text">Avoid the walls, hitting them will result in a drone crash and a restart of the game</string>
    <string name="tutorial_insurance_image3_text">Indicates a visited room, game finishes when each room is lit up</string>
    <string name="tutorial_media_use_case">Media</string>
    <string name="tutorial_media_game_use_case">Gathering boat chase footage</string>
    <string name="tutorial_media_use_case_description">A criminal is trying to escape by boat, cover the chase for the news station by following with a drone</string>
    <string name="tutorial_media_game_description">Keep the drone within the circle to gather the footage, move outside and the game restarts</string>
    <string name="tutorial_media_image1_text">Your drone marker, control with arrow keys</string>
    <string name="tutorial_media_image2_text">The target, keep moving within the circle to finish the game</string>
    <string name="tutorial_media_image3_text">Avoid the red obstacles, hitting one will restart the game</string>
    <string name="tutorial_energy_use_case">Energy</string>
    <string name="tutorial_energy_game_use_case">Pipeline inspection</string>
    <string name="tutorial_energy_use_case_description">Inspect the oil pipeline to ensure that it is in good condition</string>
    <string name="tutorial_energy_game_description">Move the drone over the pipeline, each move counts as a point and game finishes after getting a certain number of points</string>
    <string name="tutorial_energy_image1_text">Your drone marker, control with arrow keys</string>
    <string name="tutorial_energy_image2_text">The pipeline, move within this to score points</string>
    <string name="tutorial_energy_image3_text">The red squares mark the spots already visited</string>
    <string name="tutorial_healthcare_use_case">Healthcare</string>
    <string name="tutorial_healthcare_game_use_case">Deliver medical supplies</string>
    <string name="tutorial_healthcare_use_case_description">Houston has flooded and people around the city need emergency medical supplies</string>
    <string name="tutorial_healthcare_game_description">Gather supplies by entering the landing zone after each drop and deliver to each of the green markers</string>
    <string name="tutorial_healthcare_image1_text">Your drone marker, control with arrow keys</string>
    <string name="tutorial_healthcare_image2_text">Supply point, enter the circle to deliver supplies</string>
    <string name="tutorial_healthcare_image3_text">Landing zone, move within this when the drone is blue to gather more supplies</string>
    <string name="no_drone_name">NoDrone</string>

</resources>
